

# Guillaume Trompette

Consultant



8 June 1983



France



+352 661 861 983



guillaume.trompette@gmail.com

#### About me —

IT and business consultant, my position extends top-bottom from business to development teams.

I've been working for almost ten years in telecom, insurances and fund industry building complex backend systems. I enjoy working with business and IT to build or improve applications and systems to facilitate day to day business.

# Skill

Oracle

SQL and PL-SQL

Architecture

Multifonds

Scripting

Java

#### French\*6 English\*5 German\*1

(\*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

#### **interests**

Building solutions to help business teams.

### experience

since 2015 Consultant at Ike working for ITEC Societe Generale

Luxembourg

- Implementation of the BI Tool for a warehouse based on Multifonds Transfert Agent using Microstrategy
- Building architecture of the new WEM automation and monitoring tool
- Swift mt103 messaging workflow review and transformation
- · Part of Scrum team

2013-2015 Technical consultant in Multifonds

Luxembourg, Canada

- Member of support team
- Migration project for Multifonds in Winnipeg, Canada
  - Implementation, configuration and maintenance of the Multifonds Fund Accounting
  - Involvement on migration process (scripts, issues analysis etc.)
  - Daily support for production (Jira ticketing)
  - Training for new joiners
- · Management of internal installer tool development
  - Raise change requests to development
  - Manage delivery planning
  - Test the application
  - Validation of the developments
- · Creation of monitoring tool for middleware servers
  - Specifications
  - Development (Perl and Python) and packaging
  - Documentation and presentation
- WebLogic competencies
  - Installation (WebLogic stack), Administration (creation of managed servers, data sources, users etc.) and Maintenance
  - Scripting (wlst scripts, jmx scripts)
  - BI publisher

2007-2013 Consultant

France

- June 2012 to October 2013:
  - Axione, Paris, France as Software Engineer
- June 2008 to June 2012:
  - Prevadies, Nancy, France as SI Migration Engineer.
    Software development for SI migration project
- December 2007 to June 2008:
  - SETIB (Orange Group), Epinal, France as Maintenance Officer
- February 2007 to August 2007:
  - Web Developer

### education

2007 Engineer Nancy, France

Engineer school in science and technology.

2003 DUT GEII Saint Die, France

Genie Electriaque et Informatique Industrielle

## Technologies used

Microstrategy, Oracle, Multifonds, Java, Weblogic, PL-SQL, Salesforce, Perl, Python, Javascript, ACCESS